Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Labor Movement Serials WAG.345
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Labor unions and organizations, 1890-2012; 72.1 Linear Feet in 19 record cartons, 29 manuscript boxes, 2 half manuscript boxes, and 152 flat boxes
  - Subseries I.E: Education Workers, 1921-2006; 9.7 Linear Feet in 3 record cartons, 6 manuscript boxes, and 15 flat boxes
    - DuShane Fund Reports: National Education Association, Washington, DC, 1972; cuid10312 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - NEA News: National Education Association, Washington, DC, 1972; cuid10313 (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - NEA Reporter: National Education Association, Washington, DC, 1972; cuid10314 (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - NEA Research Memo: National Education Association, Washington, DC, 1971; cuid10315 (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - Washington Memo on Federal Education Programs: National Education Association, Washington, DC, 1971-1972; cuid10316 (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - What's Happening Today: National Education Association, Washington, DC, 1971; cuid10317 (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - New Jersey Teacher: New Jersey State Federation of Teachers / Trade Union Service, New York, NY, 1946 (Box 213, Folder 4)
    - New Jersey Teachers: New Jersey State Federation of Teachers, Newark, NJ, 1945, 1965; cuid10318 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - College Newsletter: New York College Teachers Union - Local 537, New York, NY, 1938-1942; cuid10319 (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - NYEA Advocate: New York Educators Association, Albany, NY, 1976; cuid10320 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - NYSTA Research: 1971-72 Teachers Salary Schedules and Selected Agreement Provisions: New York State Teachers Association - Research Division, Albany, NY, cuid10321 (Box 26, Folder 36)
    - 1972 Delegate Handbook: New York State Teachers Association (NYSTA), Albany, NY, cuid10322 (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - Challenger: New York State Teachers Association (NYSTA), Albany, NY, 1971-1972; cuid10323 (Box 30, Folder 1-2)
    - Constitution and Bylaws: New York State Teachers Association (NYSTA), Albany, NY, 1971; cuid10324 (Box 26, Folder 38)
    - EO News: New York State Teachers Association (NYSTA), Albany, NY, 1970; cuid10325 (Box 172, Folder 15)
    - Guide Lines for Local Leaders: New York State Teachers Association (NYSTA), Albany, NY, 1971-1972; cuid10326 (Box 26, Folder 39)
    - Legislative Bulletin: New York State Teachers Association (NYSTA), Albany, NY, 1971-1972; cuid10327 (Box 26, Folder 40)
    - NYSTA News Trends: New York State Teachers Association (NYSTA), Albany, NY, 1970-1971; cuid10328 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Active NYSUT Retiree: New York State United Teachers - Editorial Board of the Retirees Organizing Committee, Albany, NY, 1988-1989; cuid10329 (Box 26, Folder 41)
    - Legislative Memorandum: New York State United Teachers (AFT, AFL-CIO/NYS AFL-CIO), Albany, NY, 1990; cuid10330 (Box 26, Folder 42)
    - Benefits Newsletter: New York University, New York, NY, 1997; cuid10331 (Box 26, Folder 43)
    - N.Y.U. Workers Voice: New York University, New York, NY, 1972 (Box 194, Folder 8)
    - NTU Bulletin: Newark Teachers Union - Local 481 (AFT, AFL-CIO), Newark, NJ, 1965, 1970; cuid10332 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Red Pencil: Radical Teachers Group, Boston, MA, 1971; cuid10333 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - SCTA Speak Out: Sachem Central Teacher's Association, Lake Ronkokoma, NY, 1989-1990; cuid10334 (Box 26, Folder 44)
    - ILR Alumni Bulletin: School of Industrial and Labor Relations, Ithaca, NY, 1995; cuid10335 (Box 26, Folder 45)
    - Seattle Labor School News: Seattle Labor School, Seattle, WA, 1946; cuid10336 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Teachers' Cause: Teachers' Cause, Alexandria, VA, 1974; cuid10337 (Box 26, Folder 51)
    - Why did they fire my teacher?: Teachers Defense Committee, Los Angeles, CA, 1954; cuid10338 (Box 26, Folder 46)
    - Hey Teach!: Teachers for a Democratic Society, New York, N.Y., 1967; cuid10339 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Newsletter: Teachers Freedom Party, New York, NY, 1968 (Box 181, Folder 12)
    - Education for Democracy - Annual Educational Conference: Teachers Union - Local 5, New York, NY, 1938-1939; cuid10340 (Box 26, Folder 47)
    - Washington, D.C. Teacher: Teachers Union - Local 6 (AFT, AFL-CIO), Washington, DC, 1967; cuid10341 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Schools and the fight for peace and freedom - Teachers Union Annual Yearbook: Teachers Union of New York, Local 555, circa 1940s; cuid10342 (Box 26, Folder 48)
    - College Newsletter: Teachers Union of New York, Local 555 (UPW, CIO) - College Chapter, New York, NY, 1947; cuid10343 (Box 26, Folder 49)
    - Pension Primer: Teachers Union of the City of New York, New York, NY, 1961; cuid10344 (Box 26, Folder 50)
    - Teaching for Change: Teaching for Change, Washington, DC, 2006; cuid10345 (Box 26, Folder 52)
    - Labor Education News: UCLA Center for Labor Research & Education, Los Angeles, CA, 1992-1993; cuid10346 (Box 26, Folder 53)
    - Bulletin: Union of Private School Teachers, New York, NY, 1934; cuid10347 (Box 26, Folder 54)
    - City University UFCCT Reporter: United Federation of College Teachers, New York, NY, 1965-1966; cuid10348 (Box 26, Folder 55)
    - UFCT University Reporter: United Federation of College Teachers, New York, NY, 1966; cuid10349 (Box 26, Folder 56)
    - ATSS/UFT Journal: United Federation of Teachers, New York, NY, 1991; cuid10350 (Box 26, Folder 57)
    - Community College UFT Reporter: United Federation of Teachers, New York, NY, 1961; cuid10351 (Box 26, Folder 58)
    - Contract Update/Contract Bulletin: United Federation of Teachers, New York, NY, 1996, 2000, 2001; cuid10352 (Box 26, Folder 59)
    - Insider: United Federation of Teachers, New York, NY, 1991-1992; cuid10353 (Box 26, Folder 60, Box 183, Folder 10)
    - Last Week at The UFT: United Federation of Teachers, New York, NY, 1981-1982; cuid10354 (Box 26, Folder 61)
    - Newsletter: United Federation of Teachers, New York, NY, 1981; cuid10355 (Box 26, Folder 62)
    - UFT Bulletin: United Federation of Teachers, New York, NY, 1990-1992; cuid10356 (Box 31, Folder 1-3)
    - UFT Political Action Reporter: United Federation of Teachers, New York, NY, 1979; cuid10357 (Box 26, Folder 63)
    - UFT Professional Bulletin Board: United Federation of Teachers, New York, NY, 1989; cuid10358 (Box 26, Folder 64)
    - UFT Relay: United Federation of Teachers, New York, NY, 1981; cuid10359 (Box 26, Folder 65)
    - UFT Update: United Federation of Teachers, New York, NY, 1984; cuid10360 (Box 26, Folder 66)
    - United Teacher: United Federation of Teachers, New York, NY, 1960-1971; cuid10361 (Box 33, Folder 1-7, Box 34, Folder 1-5, Box 35, Folder 1-10, Box 36, Box 37, Box 1-4, Box 38, Folder 9)
    - United Teacher Magazine: United Federation of Teachers, New York, NY, 1971; cuid10362 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Delegate Assembly - minutes: United Federation of Teachers - Local 2 (AFT, AFL-CIO), New York, NY, 1987-1991; cuid10363 (Box 26, Folder 67)
    - Issues in Education: United Federation of Teachers - Local 2 (AFT, AFL-CIO), New York, NY, circa 1970; cuid10364 (Box 26, Folder 68)
    - UFT United Action: United Federation of Teachers - Local 2 (AFT, AFL-CIO), New York, NY, 1986; cuid10365 (Box 26, Folder 69)
    - United Teacher: United Federation of Teachers, Local 2, New York, NY, 1961 (Box 210, Folder 12)
    - United Teacher (New York City Edition): United Federation of Teachers - Local 2 (AFT, AFL-CIO), New York, NY, 1972; cuid10366 (Box 32, Folder 3-5)
    - Where We Stand: United Federation of Teachers - Local 2 (AFT, AFL-CIO), New York, NY, 1971; cuid10367 (Box 26, Folder 70)
    - UFT Chapter Newsletter: United Federation of Teachers - Local 2, American Federation of Teachers (AFL-CIO), New York, NY, 1977-1982, 1984-1986; cuid10368 (Box 26, Folder 71)
    - Damrosch Digest: United Federation of Teachers - Local 2, American Federation of Teachers (AFL-CIO) - Junior High School 136, Bx. Chapter, Bronx, NY, 1961; cuid10369 (Box 26, Folder 72)
    - New Coalition: United Federation of Teachers - New Coalition Caucus, New York, NY, 1970; cuid10370 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Magazine Page: United Federation of Teachers - Retired Teachers' Chapter, New York, NY, 1985-1986; cuid10371 (Box 26, Folder 73)
    - Membership Meeting - minutes: United Federation of Teachers - Retired Teachers' Chapter, New York, NY, 1987-1990; cuid10372 (Box 26, Folder 74)
    - RTC/UFT Monthly Newsletter: United Federation of Teachers - Retired Teachers' Chapter, New York, NY, 1988-1991; cuid10373 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - RTC-UFT Retiree: United Federation of Teachers - Retired Teachers' Chapter, New York, NY, 1987-1991; cuid10374 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - RTC-UFT Update: United Federation of Teachers - Retired Teachers' Chapter, New York, NY, 1988, 1990, 1991; cuid10375 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Legislative Committee: United Federation of Teachers - Retired Teachers' Chapter, Local 2 (AFT, AFL-CIO), New York, NY, 1990; cuid10376 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - UFT Retired Action: United Federation of Teachers - Retired Teachers' Chapter, Local 2 (AFT, AFL-CIO), New York, NY, 1985-1986; cuid10377 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Si Beagle Learning Centers Program: United Federation of Teachers - Retired Teachers' Chapter/Welfare Fund, New York, NY, 1989-1991; cuid10378 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Special EDition: United Federation of Teachers - Teacher Center Professional Development Program, New York, NY, 1987, 1991-1994, 1997, 2000-2002; cuid10379 (Box 27, Folder 6-7)
    - Retiree Advocate: United Federation of Teachers - Teachers Action Caucus, Member of the New Action Coalition, Brooklyn, NY, 1990-1991; cuid10380 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Pension News: United Federation of Teachers Pension Committee, New York, NY, 1989; cuid10381 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - News From the War Zone - Staley Workers' Solidarity Report: United Paperworkers International Union/Allied Industrial Workers of America (UPIU/AIW) - Local 7837 - War Zone Education Foundation, Decatur, IL, 1993-1996, 1999; cuid10382 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Laurel Williams' Layoff Must Be Prevented mobilization leaflet: United Staff Association of NYU Local 3882 (NYSUT, AFT, AFL-CIO), New York, NY, circa 1970s; cuid10383 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - United Teacher (New York State Edition): United Teachers of New York State/AFT (AFL-CIO), New York, NY, 1972; cuid10384 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Unity Committee Election News: Unity Committee, New York, NY, circa 1970s; cuid10385 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Labor Education Newsletter: Virginia Polytechnic Institute College of Business, Blacksburg, VA, 1968; cuid10386 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Reuther Library Newsletter: Walter P. Reuther Library, Detroit, MI, 1991, 1997, 1999-2000; cuid10387 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Report of the Executive Committee: Workers Education Bureau of America, New York, NY, 1948; cuid10388 (Box 172, Folder 17)
    - Workers Education in the United States 1929-1933: Workers Education Bureau of America, New York, NY, cuid10389 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Workers Education Center Bulletin: Workers Education Center, New York, NY, 1987; cuid10390 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - 189 News: Workers' Education Local 189, Detroit, MI, 1982-1983; cuid10391 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Newsletter: Workers' Education Local 189, Lynn, MA, 1995-1997; cuid10392 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Union News: Workers' Education Local 189, New York, NY, 1960; cuid10393 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Winter Conference: Workers' Education Local 189, Washington, DC, 1968; cuid10394 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Subseries I.F: Entertainment, 1932-1999; 4.7 Linear Feet in 3 record cartons, 1 manuscript box, and 4 flat boxes
    This series collects serials, bulletins, and newsletters issued by unions representing workers in the entertainment industry, including several publications issued by the American Federation of Television and Radio Artists; the International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees; and by local chapters of the National Association of Broadcast Employees & Technicians.
    - AFTRA/Thoughts: AFTRA-Twin Cities Local, Minneapolis, MN, 1984; cuid10395 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - AFRA File: American Federation of Radio Artists, New York, NY, 1949; cuid10396 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Stand By!: American Federation of Radio Artists, New York, NY, 1968-1981; cuid10397 (Box 23, Folder 16, Box 198)
    - On the Air: American Federation of Radio Arts, New York, NY, 1948, 1951-1952; cuid10398 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - AFTRA 1958-1960 National code of fair practice for recorder commercials for television broadcasting purposes: American Federation of Television and Radio Artists, New York, NY, cuid10399 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - AFTRA's 30th Anniversary Ball ephemera: American Federation of Television and Radio Artists, New York, NY, 1967; cuid10400 (Box 172, Folder 70)
    - Executive Secretary's Letter: American Federation of Television and Radio Artists, New York, NY, 1967; cuid10401 (Box 162, Folder 20)
    - Your 1958 Convention: American Federation of Television and Radio Artists, New York, NY, cuid10402 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Stand By!: American Federation of Television and Radio Artists - New York Local, New York, NY, 1951, 1984; cuid10403 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Official Journal of Local 802 A.F. of M.: Associated Musicians of Greater New York - Local 802 (AFM), 1932-1934; cuid10404 (Box 23, Folder 29, Box 38, Folder 13)
    - ACTRAScope: Association of Canadian Television and Radio Artists, Toronto, Canada, 1972; cuid10405 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Flash: Graphic Artists Guild, New York, NY, 1976; cuid10406 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - East Coast News Notes: International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees (IATSE) - Eastern Region, Local 600, New York, NY, 1997-1998; cuid10407 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Call Sheet: International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees (IATSE) - Locals 600 & 161, New York, NY, 1992-1997; cuid10408 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Call Sheet: International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees (IATSE) - Locals 644 & 161, New York, NY, 1992-1995; cuid10409 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - IATSE Official Bulletin: International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees, Moving Picture Technicians, Artists and Allied Crafts of the United States and Canada (IATSE) (AFL-CIO, CLC), New York, NY, 1989-1992, 1996; cuid10410 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Photographed...by: International Photographers of the Motion Picture Industry (IATSE) - Local 644, New York, NY, 1943-1946, 1952; cuid10411 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Art Works: Labor Heritage Foundation, Washington, DC, 1990-1994; cuid10412 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Labor Stage: Labor Stage, Inc., New York, NY, 1939; cuid10413 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Lab-Log: Motion Picture Laboratory Technician - Local 702 (IATSE), New York, NY, 1949; cuid10414 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Local 15 in Focus: National Association of Broadcast Employees & Technicians (NABET), New York, NY, 1990; cuid10415 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - NABET 15 in Focus: National Association of Broadcast Employees & Technicians (NABET), New York, NY, 1982-1990; cuid10416 (Box 25, Folder 1-2)
    - NABET News: National Association of Broadcast Employees & Technicians (NABET), Chicago, IL, 1962; cuid10417 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - NABET News: National Association of Broadcast Employees & Technicians (NABET), New York, NY, 1978-1999; cuid10418 (Box 25, Folder 3-4)
    - NABET Newsletter: National Association of Broadcast Employees & Technicians (NABET), Scarsdale, NY, 1975; cuid10419 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - In Focus: National Association of Broadcast Employees & Technicians (NABET) - Local 15, New York, NY, 1990; cuid10420 (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - NABET 15 Highlights: National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians - Local 15, 1981-1982; cuid10421 (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Work Lines: Ontario Workers Arts and Heritage Center, Hamilton, Ontario, Canada, 1998; cuid10422 (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Labor's Challenge: Photo-History Magazine, Concord, NH, 1937; cuid10423 (Box 173, Folder 8)
    - Screen Actor News Hollywood: Screen Actors Guild, Hollywood, CA, 1972-1973; cuid10424 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - San Francisco Actor: Screen Actors Guild - San Francisco Branch, San Francisco, CA, 1983; cuid10425 (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - Sound Track: Screen Office and Professional Employees Guild - Local 109 (United Office and Professional Workers of America, CIO), New York, NY, 1944; cuid10426 (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - Screen Writer: Screen Writers Guild, Hollywood, CA, 1947; cuid10427 (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - Made in U.S.A.: WGBH Educational Foundation, Boston, MA, 1978-1984; cuid10428 (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - Musicians' Voice: New York, NY, 1963; cuid10429 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - People's Songs, 1946-1947; cuid10430 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Subseries I.G: Farmworkers and Agricultural Unions, 1932-2002; 2.5 Linear Feet in 1 record carton, 1 manuscript box, and 4 flat boxes
    Representing farmers and agricultural laborers, this series collects serials and newspapers documenting boycotts, battles for workers' rights, conditions for migrant laborers, and changes in regulations impacting farm work more generally. The series includes some Spanish-language publications, including el Malcriado and Huelga.
    - Iowa Union Farmer: B.H. Shearer, Columbus Junction, IA, 1954; cuid10431 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Consumer-Farmer Cooperator: Consumer-Farmer Milk Cooperative, Inc., Queens, NY, 1957; cuid10432 (Box 49, Folder 60)
    - Long Island Farmworker: Eastern Farm Workers Association, Bellport, NY, 1986-1993; cuid10433 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Bulletin: Farm Credit Administration Cooperative Division, Washington, DC, 1936; cuid10434 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Nuestra lucha: Farm Labor Organizing Committee (AFL-CIO), Toledo, OH, 2002; cuid10435 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - News Bulletin: Farmer-Labor Party, Omaha, NE, 1932; cuid10436 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Farmers Defender: Farmers Defender, Inc., Ogdensburg, NY, 1947; cuid10437 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - National Union Farmer: Farmers Educational and Co-operative Union of America and National Farmers Union Life Insurance Association, Denver, CO, 1948; cuid10438 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Farmers Make Their Own Program - First and Second Farmers National Relief Conference: Farmers National Committee for Action, Washington, DC, 1933 (Box 201, Folder 2)
    - Farmworker Justice News: Farmworker Justice Fund, Inc., Washington, DC, 1997; cuid10439 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Salinas Strike & Lettuce Boycott: Inter-Faith Committee, Los Angeles, CA, 1971; cuid10440 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Wisconsin Commonwealth: Labor-Farm Party, Madison, WI, 1985-1987; cuid10441 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Farm Labor Organizing: National Advisory Committee on Farm Labor, New York, NY, 1967; cuid10442 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Agricultural Life and Labor: National Council on Agricultural Life and Labor, Washington, DC, 1957; cuid10443 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - News Service: National Farm Labor Union (AFL), Washington, DC, 1949; cuid10444 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - NFWM Newsletter: National Farm Worker Ministry, Los Angeles, CA, 1975; cuid10445 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Washington Newsletter: National Farmers Union, Denver, CO, 1988; cuid10446 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Huelga: Partido la Raza Unida, San Fernando, CA, circa 1970s; cuid10447 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Tobacco Worker / Tobacco Workers International Union: Tobacco Workers International Union, Washington, DC, 1977-1978; cuid10448 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Union Digest: Tobacco Workers International Union - Local 185, Louisville, Ky, 1940; cuid10449 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - U.S. Farm News: U.S. Farmers Association, Denison, IA, 2002 (Box 211, Folder 2)
    - New York Boycott Action Report: United Farm Workers of America (AFL-CIO), New York, NY, circa 1970s; cuid10450 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Boycott News: United Farm Workers of America AFL-CIO, Boston, MA, 1976 (Box 231, Folder 3)
    - El Malcriado, 1974; cuid10451 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - New York Labor News Protect the Migrant Worker, 1960-1980; cuid10452 (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Rural Worker: New York, NY, 1935; cuid10453 (Box 50, Folder 7, Box 159, Folder 9)
    - Southern Voice: Leesville, LA, 1935; cuid10454 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Subseries I.H: Maritime Workers, 1914-2001; 12.25 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons, 8 manuscript boxes, and 26 flat boxes
    This series collects newspapers and serials published by some of the large American maritime unions -- International Longshoreman's Association; International Organization of Masters, Mates and Pilots -- at both the organizational and rank and file level. Significant tiles include variations on the NMU Pilot; The Sextant; and a concentration of material documenting maritime work in Philadelphia (ILA News; ILA Voice; Philadelphia Longshoreman; Dockers News).
    - Waterfront News: AFL Longshore Committee, 1954-1959; cuid10455 (Box 49, Folder 17-18)
    - Philadelphia Longshoreman: AFL Longshoremen in Philadelphia, Philadelphia, PA, 1953; cuid10456 (Box 173, Folder 18)
    - Proceedings: International Longshoremen's & Warehousemen's Union, Los Angeles, CA, 1994 (Box 206, Folder 2)
    - Proceedings: International Longshoremen's & Warehousemen's Union, Seattle, WA, 1991 (Box 207, Folder 3)
    - Voice of the ILWU: International Longshoremen's & Warehouse Union - Hawaii Local 142, Honolulu, HI, 2001; cuid10470 (Box 49, Folder 29)
    - President Reports: International Longshoremen's Association, New York, NY, 1971 (Box 200, Folder 8, Box 182, Folder 2)
    - Report of Internationational Secretary-Treasurer John J. Joyce: International Longshoremen's Association, New York, NY, Undated (Box 204, Folder 5)
    - 1814 Union News: International Longshoreman's Association (AFL-CIO), Brooklyn, NY, 1980; cuid10457 (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - Enlightner: International Longshoreman's Association (AFL-CIO), Washington, DC, 1954; cuid10458 (Box 49, Folder 20)
    - ILA Checker: International Longshoreman's Association (AFL-CIO), New York, NY, 1940; cuid10459 (Box 49, Folder 21)
    - Local 824 Bulletin: International Longshoreman's Association (AFL-CIO), New York, NY, 1968-1980; cuid10460 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Longshore News: International Longshoreman's Association (AFL-CIO), New York, NY, 1950, 1956, 1965-1971; cuid10461 (Box 50, Folder 9-11)
    - Longshoreman: International Longshoreman's Association (AFL-CIO), Erie, PA, 1914, 1942, 1946, 1948-1949; cuid10462 (Box 49, Folder 22, Box 159, Folder 8)
    - Longshoremen's News: International Longshoreman's Association (AFL-CIO), New Orleans, LA, 1938; cuid10463 (Box 49, Folder 23)
    - Longshoremen's Voice: International Longshoreman's Association (AFL-CIO), New York, NY, 1970-1971; cuid10464 (Box 49, Folder 24)
    - New 1814: International Longshoreman's Association (AFL-CIO), Brooklyn, NY, 1978; cuid10465 (Box 49, Folder 25)
    - Officers' Washington Report: International Longshoreman's Association (AFL-CIO), Washington, DC, 1976-1978, 1980; cuid10466 (Box 49, Folder 26)
    - Port Messenger: International Longshoreman's Association (AFL-CIO), New York, NY, 1967; cuid10467 (Box 172, Folder 18)
    - Voice of 856: International Longshoreman's Association (AFL-CIO), New York, NY, 1955-1956; cuid10468 (Box 49, Folder 27)
    - Rank and File Longshoreman: International Longshoreman's Association (AFL-CIO) - Rank and File Committee, New York, NY, 1945-1946; cuid10469 (Box 49, Folder 28)
    - Report of the Secretary-Treasurer Harry R. Hasselgren and Minutes of Executive Council: International Longshoremen's Association Independent, New York, NY, 1953-1957 (Box 204, Folder 2)
    - Sextant: International Organization of Masters, Mates, and Pilots, San Francisco, CA, 1953-1957, 1959-1970; cuid10471 (Box 56, Folder 1-6, Box 58, Folder 1-3)